<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<gallery>
  <uniqueid>36326762</uniqueid>
  <title><![CDATA[View of the news]]></title>
  <date>2018-01-10T10:32:01-0800</date>
  <category>photo</category>
  <taxonomy>32058195</taxonomy>
  <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
  <images>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Darrell and Jeanne Walker pass under a Magnolia tree while on an afternoon walk around Owen Rose Garden. Established in 1951, the 8.5 acre garden sits nestled next to the Willamette River near the Washington Jefferson Street bridge. (Collin Andrew/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Collin Andrew]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.magnolia.01.0330.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Blake Stevens stands frozen as the Renaissance sculptor, painter and architect Michelangelo during the 6th Annual Living Wax Museum at Dos Rios Elementary School in Springfield Thursday. Fifth-grade students completed research projects on famous subjects from the worlds of science, technology, engineering, arts and mathematics by dressing as their subjects and when prompted, reciting what they learned. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.waxmuseum.0323.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Traffic creeps through the Whiteaker neighborhood along West First Avenue as a rainy sunset dresses the Coast Range in golden hues. Forecasts call for showers and rain in the Eugene and Springfield area through Sunday, with highs in the mid- to high 40s and lows in the mid- to low 30s. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.rain.03xx.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Members of the Eugene-Springfield Junior Orchestra wait in the wings while listening to the brass section play a piece during one of the group's two outreach concerts they performed for nearly 900 Springfield elementary school children Wednesday at the Springfield High School auditorium. The orchestra has 53 youth musicians from 20 different schools and is conducted by Christopher Noel. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.ESYO_1.0322.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Eugene-Springfield Junior Orchestra cellist Breanna Raven warms up for the second of two outreach concerts she performed with fellow musicians for nearly 900 Springfield elementary school children Wednesday at the Springfield High School auditorium. The orchestra has 53 youth musicians from 20 different schools and is conducted by Christopher Noel. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.ESYO_2.0322.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Eugene-Springfield Junior Orchestra conductor Christopher Noel conducts during the group's outreach performance for Springfield elementary school children Wednesday at the Springfield High School auditorium. Nearly 900 schoolchildren attended the two performances. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.ESYO_5.0322.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Joel Vila (left) visiting from Spain and Hannah Salbador enjoy a picnic on the gardens in Hendricks Park in Eugene. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.Hendricks02cp.0321.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Josh the Goldendoodle was taking more of an observational role rather than that of supervision as he watched Jon Weck weed among his lavender bed at Weck's home on Lincoln Street in Eugene. The lavender will provide a bank of color for the front of Weck's home of more than 40 years when the blooms come onto the plants. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.FeatureMonday_2.0320.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Rebecca Marx, grant writer for Looking Glass Community Services, assembles a lamp Thursday in one of four newly renovated apartments in a building that houses the Looking Glass New Roads runaway and homeless youth shelter on West Seventh Avenue in Eugene. From left, Ashlee Jacobson and Brett Mathews of SELCO, which provided the funding for the transitional center&rsquo;s new home furnishings, assemble the apartment necessities with Mason Moorman (center), development coordinator for Looking Glass. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.LookingGlass.0316.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Blooming daffodils grace the path as students make their way to and from class on the University of Oregon campus in Eugene. The 46th annual Long Tom Grange Daffodil Festival, the largest daffodil festival in the state, will be Saturday, March 17 and Sunday, March 18. The festival begins and ends with a free shuttle ride from Conser Quarry on Ferguson Road to the historic Long Tom Grange in Junction City with miles of country roads showing off a dazzling display of wild growing roadside daffodils. Rain or shine, the event offers vendor booths, food, raffles, a quilt show, live music and daffodil sales.  Beside the spring blooms, another main attraction of the festival is the cinnamon rolls, baked fresh by New Day Bakery in Eugene. &ldquo;Most importantly, we have almost 300 local volunteers who help make this festival a true community experience," said festival organizer Danuta Pfeiffer. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.daffodils.03xx.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Grammy Award-winning cellist Zuill Bailey plays music for University of Oregon students in the Oregon Plaza of the EMU on campus as part of his week-long residency with the Eugene Symphony. Bailey will be performing at a variety of locations this week before joining the symphony at the Hult Center Thursday night for a performance of Tales of Hemingway. For more information visit: eugenesymphony.org. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.Cellist.0314.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Warm weather Monday helped Ted Dearborn tackle the task of preparing for planting at the Amazon Community Garden in south Eugene. Dearborn plans to plant potatoes in this particular plot while other spots are reserved for onions and garlic.  (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.weather_1.0313.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Jungah Lee, right, poses under a flowering tree on the University of Oregon campus as Jun Lang takes her photograph Monday. Recent warm weather has helped flowering trees blossom in the area.  (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.weather_2.0313.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Decked out for a road trip with his &ldquo;Doggles&rdquo; for eye protection, Max the dog licks his chops in anticipation of a treat during a stop at The Greatfull Grind coffee kiosk with his owner Tyler Chrowl Wednesday. Max and Chrowl are regular customers at the Springfield Gateway area coffee shop and Max looks forward to treats and icecubes during the visits. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.Doggles01.0310.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[An egret takes flight over farm fields along Highbanks Road in Springfield Ore. Friday, March 2, 2018. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.egret.0309.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Puddle Jumper Towing diver Daniel Bennett prepares to attach a submerged RV to get towed in at Dexter Lake, March 7th, 2018.  A driver and his dog were rescued unharmed.   (Kelly Lyon/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Kelly Lyon]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.waterrescue.006.0308.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Thurston Elementary School fifth grade students Kendall Carey, left, and Jack Henricks close in on finishing construction of their LEGO diesel engine during Cummins Diesel Days Wednesday at the Springfield school. Students built the engine and, as part of a Career Technical Education componenet, learned about career options, including engineering, sale, service, part and business operation. Last year, as fourth graders, the students learned the science behind the diesel combustion engine. Employees from Cummins Diesel were on hand to help students with the project.  (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.DieselDays_01.0308_.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Team Run Hub running coach Brett Ely (center) and the rest of the team warm up to songs from a portable speaker before heading out or their training run. Members of the group are training for the Eugene Marathon later this year, but are still working out the logistics of taking the speaker along. At 30 lbs Ely said with a laugh that, "carrying it on her back," for the whole marathon is not an option. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.RunHub01.0307.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Dressed as the mythical phoenix, 7-year-old Rosalyn Casita, from Eugene, joins dozens of other children in creating art projects during the Emerald Empire Reading Council&rsquo;s annual &ldquo;Be Excited About Reading&rdquo; or B.E.A.R. Faire at the Springfield City Hall atrium in Springfield. The Saturday event, which has been going on for over 30 years, is put on by a group of present and retired school teachers who volunteer their Saturday to make free books available to area children and supervise the art activies. As a bonus, children, like Casita, who came to the afternoon play day dressed as storybook character got to choose an extra book. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.bearfaire01.0304.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[A happy bicyclist rides with an umbrella hat near Maurie Jacobs Park on a wet Wednesday.  (Kelly Lyon/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Kelly Lyon]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.linesonly.001.KL.0301.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Rain over the weekend gave way to sun on Monday and a jogger took advantage of the break to travel under a flowering cherry tree along the Willamette River near Ferry Street Bridge in Eugene. For Tuesday there is slight chance of rain before 10 a.m., then a slight chance of showers after 10 a.m. The skies will be cloudy with a high near 44. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.MondayFeature_01.0227.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[A visitor at Fern Ridge reservoir walks along the dam east of Eugene, Ore. Monday, February 26, 2018 during sunny weather. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[OREUG102.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Cortney Hudson-Crawford (right) is embraced after snow stated to fall after a balloon release and candle lighting vigil on 54th and Main Street in Springfield on Thursday in memory of her children, John Day, 8, McKenzie Hudson, 5, and Tyler Hudson, 4, who died while crossing Main Street with their mother in 2015. (Collin Andrew/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Collin Andrew]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.memorial.ca05.0223.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Kai Francis, 12, pauses to take in the view during a family outing in the snow at Hendricks Park in Eugene after a storm dropped several inches of snow on the area. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.Snow03cp.0223.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Gavin Obley blasts Finn Horn with a fresh snowball Thursday morning in Eugene.  (Kelly Lyon/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Kelly Lyon]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.snow.KL.001.0223.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Liam Leavitt flies on the trampoline after fresh snowfall in Eugene Thursday morning.  (Kelly Lyon/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Kelly Lyon]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.snow.KL.002.0223.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Mia Francis, 8, his the slopes of Hendricks Park with her Frozen branded snow sled during a family outing in the snow Thursday. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.Snow04cp.0223.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Nine-year-old Isa Vielma (right) and her sister 13-year-old Raquel Chaney build snowballs in their driveway off Willamette Street in south Eugene on Thursday morning. (Collin Andrew/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Collin Andrew]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.snow.ca01.0223.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Jaime Hock uses a sled to get her three-year-old daughter, Maeve Hock, to preschool in Eugene on Thursday morning. (Collin Andrew/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Collin Andrew]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.snow.ca04.0223.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[A snowman sees a touch of spring in south Eugene on Thursday morning after a blanket of snow fell on the Willamette Valley on Feb. 22, 2018. (Collin Andrew/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Collin Andrew]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.snow.ca02.0223.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Sandi Thompson tries to explain that snowmen are mostly safe to her dog Missy, who is seeing the snow sculpture for the fist time while on a walk around the track at Edgewood Elementary School on Thursday. (Collin Andrew/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Collin Andrew]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.snow.ca03.0223.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Gerardo Bermudez, of Eugene, makes his way through the snow on his way up the Spencer Butte Trail Wednesday morning. The valley was largely spared of ice and snow. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.Snow01cp.0222.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Members of the Cascade Manor Can-Can Dance Group perform in the first ever Senior Talent Show at the Wow Hall on Tuesday.  (Kelly Lyon/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Kelly Lyon]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.SeniorTalent.001.0221.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[A dusting of snow on the Coburg Hills provides a wintry backdrop above Sacred Heart Medical Center at Riverbend in Springfield, Ore. Monday, February 19, 2018. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[OREUG101.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Eugene city streets were blocked off due to a suspicious device on Sunday, Feb. 18, 2018. The Eugene Police Department used a robot to investigate a pressure cooker that was located on Charnelton Street between 8th and Broadway. (Collin Andrew/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Collin Andrew]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.eugbomb.02.0219.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Greg Coakley with T&M Towing, removes flowers from the hood of a vehicle that was driven by 92-year-old Dale Stone that crashed through the floral department before stopping in the produce section of the Safeway store in Junction City. No one was injured in the incident on Sunday, Feb. 18, 2018. (Collin Andrew/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Collin Andrew]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.safewaycrash.01.0219.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Emmett Holder plays outside in a flurry of snow at the Lane Events Center. Snow, wintry mix and rain alternated with periods of sunshine on Sunday in the Eugene-Springfield area. (August Frank/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[August Frank]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.heritagefair06.0219.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Flower salesman Joey Nagler (left) talks Valentine bouquets with Hailey Woram and Kiana Jardin, both juniors at the University of Oregon, as they stop between classes to admire the display at Rhythm and Blooms flower stand in front of the University of Oregon Bookstore near campus in Eugene. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.Valentine01.0214.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[The Heron sculpture at the entrance to the University District on 13th Ave. near campus in Eugene received a heart from a creative and  anonymous benefactor for Valentine's Day. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.Valentine02.0214.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Luna the dog jumps though a hoop as she joins Chloe Christensen (left) and Persephone Lucero in a play date at the dog park in Alton Baker Park near Autzen Stadium. The trio were enjoying a sunny but cold and windy day at the park Monday afternoon. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.DogPark01.0213.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Two participants dressed as bananas take the Polar Plunge into the Willamette River to raise money for Special Olympics on Saturday, Feb. 10, 2018. (Collin Andrew/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Collin Andrew]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.polarplunge.001.0211.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Kit Frye walks along Jeppesen Acres Road to Sheldon High School on stilts Friday. Frye's commute takes her about 15 minutes. (Collin Andrew/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Collin Andrew]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.stilts.03.0210.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[The male Anna's Hummingbird can put on a spectacular iridescent display with a turn of his head, utilizing his tiny feather microstructure and the angle of the sun's rays to flash a sparkling pinkish-red head, often used in courtship displays. The bird, about the size of a ping-pong ball, is the only hummingbird to reside in Oregon year round. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.hummingbird.0208.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Sunlight plays off the waters inside Willamalane Park Swim Center as a swimmer does laps at the facility in Springfield, Ore. Monday, February 5, 2018. Sunny weather and highs near 60 degrees warmed the Willamette Valley, making for an unseasonably springlike winter day. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.sunlaps.0206.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[15-year-old Evan Myers is silhouetted in front of his art of fire dancing as he uses a mixture of fire swords and fire staffs at Washington Park in Eugene on Monday, Feb. 5, 2018. Myers spent the night practicing a routine he will perform in front of classmates at a pep rally later in the week at South Eugene High School. (Collin Andrew/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Collin Andrew]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.fire_dance.0206.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Phil Fish, from Walton, has been coming out to demonstrate almost every Tuesday for the last year near the Federal Courthouse in Eugene.  About 25 people held signs for a weekly event called Resist Trump Tuesday.  (Kelly Lyon/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Kelly Lyon]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.rally.001.02xx.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Kathleen Gartrell-Hunt demonstrates with her husband Phil Hunt near the Federal Courthouse in Eugene on February 6th, 2018.  (Kelly Lyon/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Kelly Lyon]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.rally.002.02xx.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Tasia Pachito-Miller peers up at a big bubble produced by Corey O'Neill at Skinner Butte Park along the Willamette River in Eugene. Pachito-Miller was enjoy Monday's lovely weather with her mother, Tawshma Pachito. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.FeatureMonday_AN.0206.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Don Boots casts a fishing pole while on a morning fishing trip with his grandsons Caden Etchison, 10, (pictured) and Cody Etchison, 9, along the rocks below the dam at Fern Ridge Reservoir on Friday, Feb. 2, 2018. (Collin Andrew/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Collin Andrew]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.fernridge.01.0203.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Nine-year-old Cody Banyas and his dad Mike Banyas ride a zip line at the Eugene Boat & Sportsman's Show that runs February 2nd- 4th at the Lane County Convention Center in Eugene. (Collin Andrew/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Collin Andrew]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.sportsmanshow.01.0203.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Eugene police Sgt. Julie Smith (right) pets Shaiva the German shepherd during a visit with Jared Blair and Dana Sparks on West Broadway in downtown Eugene. The law banning dogs downtown was not renewed by the City Council last fall, allowing dogs on leash back into the city core this winter. Smith has a German shepherd of her own and stopped to chat with Blair and Sparks during her patrol duties Tuesday. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.DogVisit.0131.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Eugene-Springfield Firefighters battle a large structure fire at Armur Electrostatic Powder, a sandblasting business located at 6191 Royal Ave. in Eugene. Fire officials were first called to the sandblasting business around 5:40 a.m. (Collin Andrew/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Collin Andrew]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.fire.001.0128.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Children play on a rope swing on Swing Hill in the Lane County's Buford Park over looking the confluence of the Coast Fork and Middle Fork of of the Willamette River southeast of Eugene. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.Pisgah01.0130.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[A walker strolls through Laurelwood Golf Course Monday afternoon as temperatures climbed into the 50s in Eugene. Rain is expected in the Willamette Valley on Tuesday. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.feature_AN_1.0130.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Rick Roe with Odell Lake Lodge works to clear nearly a foot of snow from roads near the resort east of Willamette Pass. A storm moving through the Cascades is expected to continue to dump consider amounts of snow in the higher elevations. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.snow_2.0125.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[A resident heron sits on a dock railing at Odell Lake Lodge as snow falls at the resort east of Willamette Pass. A storm moving through the Cascades is expected to continue to dump consider amounts of snow in the higher elevations. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.snow_5.0125.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Bryce Hanson helps his girlfriend, Sophia Marquez with her gloves during a visit to Odell Lake Lodge east of Willamette Pass. Hanson was visiting the resort from California with his aunt and uncle, Marvin Keller and Nancy Keller of Eugene. For Marquez, the visit was the first time for her to experience being in falling snow. A storm moving through the Cascades is expected to continue to dump consider amounts of snow in the higher elevations. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.snow_8.0125.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[During a break in the rain showers Wednesday, Autzen Stadium is illuminated in a shaft of sunlight just before sunset. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.Autzen.0125.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[A pair of young male Roosevelt elk spar with their antlers at the Dean Creek Elk Viewing Area near Reedsport on the Oregon coast. A mild winter climate and abundant forage allow elk to remain at refuge year-round. The site, owned and managed by the Bureau of Land Management, is about three miles east of Reedsport on Hwy. 38. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.ElkSparring.01xx.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Eleven-year-old Indiana Setter (right) and her sister Sabine Setter, 11, document the thousands that filled the courtyard and streets in front of the Wayne L. Morse U.S. Courthouse in Eugene, Ore., for the Women&rsquo;s March for Action on Saturday, Jan. 20, 2018. The Setter's who attended last years Women's March to have their voice heard, instead brought their cameras to focus on the prepossess of listening. (Collin Andrew/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Collin Andrew]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.womensmarch.011.0121.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Julia Arnold (left), from Roseburg, celebrates her birthday by watching giant waves crash on the rocks at Shore Acres State Park near Charleston with friend Cheri Knott. Waves at Shore Acres near Charleston. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.Storm01.0120.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[An umbrella protects a pedestrian from rain while walking on the sidewalk along East 13th Avenue in Eugene. Rainy conditions are expected to continue in the Willamette Valley Friday. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.rainfeature1.0119.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[The setting sun beckons a woman to make a quick photograph atop Skinner Butte in Eugene, Ore. Tuesday, January 16, 2017. Partly cloudy skies are expected to give way to rain and more wintry weather later in the week. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.wintersky.1117.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[It was not the case on Tuesday that University of Oregon advertising major Morgan Le had stumbled into "Honey, I Shrunk the Kids" protagonist Wayne Szalinski's Shrinking Machine only the illusion of such screen hijinx as Le found comfort relaxing in an oversized chair at the Erb Memorial Union on the university campus. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.feature.0117.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[The last rays of sunlight crawl up the peak of Mount Jefferson, as viewed from the summit of Spencer Butte south of Eugene, Ore. Sunday, January 14, 2018, while the Willamette Valley sits beneath a cloudy blanket, disturbed only by a plume of water vapor from the International Paper mill in Springfield. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[OREUG104.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Low clouds and fog envelop the Willamette Valley over Eugene, Ore. Sunday, January 14, 2018, as seen from the summit of Spencer Butte. Among the landmarks visible are Autzen Stadium with its iconic O and the silver facade of Matthew Knight Arena on the campus of the University of Oregon. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[OREUG103.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[A 10 inch baseball and a catchers glove that Lois Youngen of Eugene used to catch a perfect game while being one of the 550 women who played professional baseball for 4 years after WWII. Their story was told in the film ŇA League of Their Own.Ó (Collin Andrew/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Collin Andrew]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.youngen.02.0114.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Rosie the Riveter alumnus Marty Lynch, 92, (left) greets Rosebud Corolene Corriea during a meeting of other Rosies at Willamalane Senior Center in Springfield. Lynch worked as a "shortage chaser" delivering parts in a sprawling bomber plane factory in California during World War II. Corriea, who has earned the title of Rosebud because her mother Alice Riddle who passed away in 2013 was a Rosie, has continued to meet with her mother's old friends over the years. The group gathered Friday to be interviewed and photographed for a calendar project being put together by The Washington Women in Trades Association. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.Rosies01.0113.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Rosie the Riveters Anne Olsen (left) and Marty Lynch (right)  reunite to be interviewed by Robin Murphy (center) for a commemorative calendar celebrating the Rosie legacy during a day long session at the Willamalane Senior Center in Springfield. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.Rosies02.0113.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Alice Heiney (left), who just turned 100 years old last week, poses for a portrait by Robin Murphy for a calendar celebrating the Rosie legacy proceeded annually by Washington Women in Trades Association. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.Rosies03.0113.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[A great blue heron settles on the dock near the east end of Odell Lake in the Oregon Cascades. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.snowpack.07.1229.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[An unharmed dog stands in the doorway as Eugene-Springfield firefighters mop up a house fire on Greiner St. in west Eugene on Monday, Jan. 8, 2018. (Collin Andrew/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Collin Andrew]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.greinerfire.01.0109.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[A rainbow touches down in the south hills of Eugene, Ore. Friday, January 5, 2017 during a sun break on a rainy afternoon. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.rainbow.0106.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Riparian woodland reflect off a channel of the Willamette river upriver from the confluence to the McKenzie river on Saturday, Jan. 6, 2018. (Collin Andrew/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Collin Andrew]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.winter.water.01.0107.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Sheep graze under a canopy of clouds along Powerline Road north of Coburg Wednesday afternoon as dry weather continued to prevail in the Willamette Valley. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.featureAN_01.0104.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[With the holiday season giving way to a new year, Ron Renchler takes down his Christmas decorations, including a almost life size Santa Claus, at his home in the Whiteaker neighborhood of Eugene. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.ByeByeSanta.0104.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[A Townsend's warbler flies between feeders in a Eugene backyard. The strikingly-colored bird is native to coniferous forests from Alaska to Oregon but migrates into the Willamette Valley in winter. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.warbler.1227.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[The day after Christmas saw one south Eugene Santa Claus more than a little deflated after the holiday celebration. But a way in the nearby manger, the figures depicting the reason for the season were still holding steady. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.FeatureTuesdayAN1.1227.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Don Jefferis hikes down the foggy Ridgeline Trail near Fox Hollow Road Tuesdayn after climbing to the summit of Spencer Butte in Eugene. The fog lifted on much of the valley floor on Tuesday but lingered in some of the higher elevations in the area. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.FeatureTuesdayAN2.1227.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Ski instructor Micah Breshears throws up a spray of snow as he makes a snowboard a run on Headwall during opening day at Hoodoo Ski Area east of Springfield. Breshears, who lives in in Waterloo and has been an instructor of nine years, called Hoodoo Ňthe little ski area with the big heartÓ before heading off for another run Friday. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.Hoodoo01.1223.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Andy Holland carries his three-year-old daughter Josie Holland to the lodge during a day of skiing on opening day at Hoodoo Ski Area east of Springfield. The Hollands, from Camas,  WA. are spending the holidays at nearby Black Butte. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.Hoodoo02.1223.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Anne Borland from Eugene cross country skis into a cabin near Hoodoo Ski Area on opening day at the ski area east of Springfield. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.Hoodoo04.1223.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[A light blanket of snow surrounds Sahalie Falls Friday. (Chris Pietsch/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Chris Pietsch]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.SahalieFalls.1223.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Dodging trees and shrubs, a sledder makes the best of the light snowpack at the Salt Creek Summit Sno-Park Thursday, December 28, 2017 near Willamette Pass in the Oregon Cascades, where the snowpack is 57 percent of normal. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.snowpack.02.1229.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[A woman walks her dog on the dock at the east end of Odell Lake in the Oregon Cascades, where the snowpack is 57 percent of normal. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.snowpack.04.1229.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Two bald eagles fly above Odell Lake in the Oregon Cascades, where the snowpack is 57 percent of normal. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.snowpack.05.1229.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Snow covers Diamond Peak above Odell Lake in the Oregon Cascades. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.snowpack.06.1229.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Ski runs at Willamette Pass await the snowpack Thursday afternoon. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.snowpack.08.1229.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[The fire pit at Shelter Cove faces the ski runs at Willamette Pass, which can be seen across Odell Lake. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.snowpack.09.1229.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Kelly Thibodeaux plays his fiddle while challenging children and parents to do the same during a performance and impromptu group lesson at the Eugene Public Library Wednesday, December 27, 2017. Thibodeaux brought his Louisiana fiddle music -- mostly songs about alligators, crawfish and swamps --  along with a bunch of half-sized fiddles to the library to encourage children to be musically aware. (Brian Davies/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Brian Davies]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[cr.fiddle02.1228.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
  </images>
</gallery>
