<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<gallery>
  <uniqueid>36428387</uniqueid>
  <title><![CDATA[Scenes from the Winter Olympics opening ceremony]]></title>
  <date>2018-02-09T08:45:34-0800</date>
  <category>photo</category>
  <taxonomy>32058784</taxonomy>
  <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
  <images>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Vice President Mike Pence, second from bottom right, sits between second lady Karen Pence, third from from bottom left, and Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe at the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. Seated behind Pence are Kim Yong Nam, third from top right, president of the Presidium of North Korean Parliament, and Kim Yo Jong, second from top right, sister of North Korean leader Kim Jong Un. (AP Photo/Patrick Semansky, Pool)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Patrick Semansky]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.194.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Erin Hamlin carries the flag of the United States during the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Charlie Riedel)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Charlie Riedel]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.423.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[The United States team walk onto the stage during the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Julie Jacobson)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Julie Jacobson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.434.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[The team from the United States walk onto the stage during the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Charlie Riedel)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Charlie Riedel]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.475.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Athletes from North and South Korea arrive during the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Matthias Schrader)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Matthias Schrader]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.403.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Greece enters the stadium during the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/David J. Phillip,Pool)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[David J. Phillip]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.155.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Fireworks explode behind the Olympic flame during the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/David J. Phillip,Pool)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[David J. Phillip]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.715.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[North Korea's Jong Su Hyon, and South Korea's Park Jong-ah carry the torch during the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Jae C. Hong)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Jae C. Hong]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.745.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[North Korea's Jong Su Hyon, left, and South Korea's Park Jong-ah carry the torch during the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/David J. Phillip,Pool)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[David J. Phillip]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.723.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[South Korean Olympic figure skating champion Yuna Kim performs before lighting the Olympic flame during the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/David J. Phillip,Pool)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[David J. Phillip]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.577.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[South Korean Olympic figure skating champion Yuna Kim lights the Olympic flame during the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/David J. Phillip,Pool)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[David J. Phillip]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.724.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[A dancer performs during the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Michael Sohn)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Michael Sohn]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.595.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Fireworks explode during the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Petr David Josek)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Petr David Josek]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.632.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Performers participate during the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Petr David Josek)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Petr David Josek]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.651.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[A makeup artist applies glitter to a performer backstage during the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Gregory Bull, Pool)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Gregory Bull]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.308.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Performers watch a monitor backstage as athletes from North and South Korea walk together during the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Gregory Bull, Pool)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Gregory Bull]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.348.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Kim Yo Jong, left, sister of North Korean leader Kim Jong Un, shakes hands with South Korean President Moon Jae-in at the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Patrick Semansky, Pool)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Patrick Semansky]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.707.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Kim Yong Nam, top left, president of the Presidium of North Korean Parliament, and Kim Yo Jong, sister of North Korean leader Kim Jong Un, top right, sit behind U.S. Vice President Mike Pence, bottom left, and Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe, bottom right, as they watch the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Patrick Semansky, Pool)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Patrick Semansky]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.596.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[South Korean President Moon Jae-in, left, stands alongside first lady Kim Jung-sook as the South Korean national anthem is played at the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Patrick Semansky, Pool)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Patrick Semansky]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.716.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Thomas Bach, president of the International Olympic Committee, speaks during the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (Clive Mason/Pool Photo via AP)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Clive Mason]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.726.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Members of the North Korean delegation sit before the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Matthias Schrader)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Matthias Schrader]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.11.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Members of the North Korean delegation hold flags of the combined Koreas before the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Matthias Schrader)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Matthias Schrader]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.12.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Members of the North Korean delegation wave flags of the combined Koreas before the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Natacha Pisarenko)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Natacha Pisarenko]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.13.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[A police officer stands outside the stadium prior to the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Christophe Ena)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Christophe Ena]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.1.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Vice President Mike Pence, right, walks to his seat alongside second lady Karen Pence at the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Patrick Semansky, Pool)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Patrick Semansky]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.377.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Kim Yo Jong, sister of North Korean leader Kim Jong Un, arrives at the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Patrick Semansky, Pool)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Patrick Semansky]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_Openin.720.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Athletes and attendees are transported following the opening ceremony of the 2018 Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang, South Korea, Friday, Feb. 9, 2018. (AP Photo/Gregorio Borgia)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Gregorio Borgia]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[Pyeongchang_Olympics_07295..jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
  </images>
  <seo-label>/rg/photo/36428387-321/scenes-from-the-winter-olympics-opening-ceremony.html.csp</seo-label>
</gallery>
