<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<gallery>
  <uniqueid>36480848</uniqueid>
  <title><![CDATA[Ducks down Devils 75-68]]></title>
  <date>2018-02-22T22:58:02-0800</date>
  <category>photo</category>
  <taxonomy>32058195</taxonomy>
  <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
  <images>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Oregon forward Kenny Wooten, right, and Oregon forward Keith Smith defend againsty Arizona State guard Remy Martin as he drives to the basket during the first half of their Pac-12 matchup at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uomen_01.0223.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Arizona State forward Mickey Mitchell and Oregon forward Troy Brown battle for a rebound during the first half of their Pac-12 matchup at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uomen_02.0223.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Oregon forward Mikyle McIntosh is challenged by Arizona State forward Romello White as he drives to the basket during the first half of their Pac-12 matchup at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uomen_03.0223.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Arizona State head coach Bobby Hurley argues a call the first half of the Sun Devils' matchup with the Ducks at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uomen_04.0223.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Arizona State guard Kodi Justice and Arizona State forward Kimani Lawrence try to steal the ball from Oregon forward Troy Brown during the first half of their Pac-12 matchup at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uomen_05.0223.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Oregon head coach Dana Altman encourages his players during the first half of their matchup with Arizona State at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uomen_06.0223.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Arizona State guard Kodi Justice gets a pass off while being defended by Oregon forward Troy Brown during the first half of their Pac-12 matchup at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uomen_07.0223.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Oregon forward Kenny Wooten challenges the shot of Arizona State guard Shannon Evans II as Oregon forward Mikyle McIntosh, Oregon guard Payton Pritchard and Oregon guard Elijah Brown watch during the second half of their Pac-12 matchup at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uomen_08.0223.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Oregon forward Troy Brown looks for an outlet pass as he is guarded by Arizona State guard Shannon Evans II during the second half of their Pac-12 matchup at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uomen_10.0223.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Oregon forward Mikyle McIntosh powers to the basket as he is defended by Arizona State forward De'Quon Lake, left, and Arizona State forward Kimani Lawrence, right,  during thye second half of their Pac-12 matchup at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uomen_09.0223.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Oregon forward Paul White has his shot blocked by Arizona State guard Shannon Evans II as Arizona State forward De'Quon Lake helps on the play during the second half of their Pac-12 matchup at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uomen_12.0223.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Oregon forward Troy Brown yells in support of Oregon forward Mikyle McIntosh after McIntosh was fouled on a shot which he made during the second quarter of their Pac-12 matchup against Arizona State at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uomen_11.0223.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
  </images>
</gallery>
