<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<gallery>
  <uniqueid>36437790</uniqueid>
  <title><![CDATA[Ducks down Cougars 84-57]]></title>
  <date>2018-02-11T19:50:02-0800</date>
  <category>photo</category>
  <taxonomy>32058195</taxonomy>
  <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
  <images>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Oregon forward Troy Brown battles with Washington State guard Malachi Flynn for the ball during the first half at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uowsumenhoops1.0212_.jpg]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Oregon forward Kenny Wooten slams the ball home over Washington State guard Malachi Flynn during the second half of the Ducks' win over the Cougars at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uowsumenhoops4.0212_.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Oregon forward Kenny Wooten flexes after dunking during the first half  Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uowsumenhoops3.0212_.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Oregon head coach Dana Altman calls out a play during the first half at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uowsumenhoops11.0212_.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Oregon guard Payton Pritchard drives to the basket as he is defended by Washington State forward Drick Bernstine in the second half at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uowsumenhoops9.0212_.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Oregon forward Kenny Wooten and Oregon forward Troy Brown combine to stop Washington State forward Jeff Pollard as he drives to the basket during the first quarter at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uowsumenhoops5.0212_.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Washington State head coach calls out a play during the first half at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uowsumenhoops12.0212_.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Oregon forward Kenny Wooten blocks the shot of Washington State guard Milan Acquaah during the first half at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uowsumenhoops2.0212_.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Washington State guard Malachi Flynn passes the ball to teammate Washington State forward Drick Bernstine as he is defended in the lane by Oregon forward Paul White during the first half Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uowsumenhoops6.0212_.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Oregon forward Abu Kigab runs into Washington State forward Drick Bernstine as they battle for a rebound in the second half at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uowsumenhoops7.0212_.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Oregon forward Troy Brown drives to the basket and is flagrantly fouled by Washington State guard Malachi Flynn late in the second hafl at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uowsumenhoops10.0212_.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Oregon forward Kenny Wooten shoots over Washington State forward Davante Cooper during the second half at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uowsumenhoops8.0212_.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <caption><![CDATA[Washington State head coach Ernie Kent scans the crowd for familiar faces after the Cougars' loss to the Ducks at Matthew Knight Arena. (Andy Nelson/The Register-Guard)]]></caption>
      <credit><![CDATA[Andy Nelson]]></credit>
      <filename><![CDATA[sp.uowsumenhoops13.0212_.JPG]]></filename>
    </image>
  </images>
  <seo-label>/rg/photo/36437790-321/ducks-down-cougars-84-57.html.csp</seo-label>
</gallery>
